Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 10: Pins and Ribbons, 1895-2000; 8 boxes
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 15)
    Orange and round with "1926" and the Princeton seal and motto in black; "GEO. COOK" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1910 50th reunion pin, 1960; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "1910," "Princeton" and "50th" in black; and "Brown Rolston" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1915 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "1915" and Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1922 25th reunion pin, 1947; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "22's BIG 25th" in black.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, 1956; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "1922," "Princeton" and "1956 Class Dinner" in black.
  - Class of 1923 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
    White and round with "1923" in black.
  - Class of 1923 23rd reunion pin, 1946; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "23's Twenty-Third," "Joe Fleming" and "'23" in black.
  - Class of 1926 25th reunion pin, 1951; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "25th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1951" in black; a caricature drawing of Nassau Hall and two tigers in black; "Charlie Millard" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 30th reunion pin, 1956; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "30th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1956" in black; a caricature drawing of a tiger lounging on the beach and smoking; "Margaretta Cook" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 40th reunion pin, 1966; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "40th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1966" in black; a tiger face drawn in black; "Orvel Sebring" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 45th reunion pin, 1971; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "45th" and "'26" in black; a drawing of a tiger lounging on the beach with a Hawaiian dancer dancing; "GEORGE COOK" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round "1926" in black.
  - Class of 1927 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
    Orange and round with "1927" in black; the Princeton seal and motto in black; "AL WHITAKER" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1909 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1909" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1910 3rd reunion pin, 1913; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "3rd Reunion" in black.
  - Class of 1910 20th reunion pin, 1930; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "Twentieth Reunion" in black.
  - Class of 1913 55th reunion pin, 1968; 1 item (Box 17)
    White and round with "1913" and "1968" in black; and "55th Reunion" in orange.
  - Class of 1922 15th reunion pin, 1937; 1 item (Box 17)
    Yellow and round with "Class of 1922," "135" and "Fifteenth Reunion" in black; "Alex Morgan" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "22" in the center, surrounded by twenty-six 2's in black.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1922" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1924 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1924" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1926 35th reunion pin, 1961; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "35th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1961" in black; a sleeping tiger drawn in black; "GEO. COOK" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1922 50th matriculation anniversary pin, 1972; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1922," "1972," "Matriculation Weekend," "Princeton" and "1926" in black; the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "1926" in black; a tiger lounging on the beach drawn in black and green.
  - Class of 1929 55th reunion pin, 1955; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "55th" and "1929" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1950; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1950" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1958; 1 item (Box 17)
    Red and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1958" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1959; 1 item (Box 17)
    Light yellow with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1959" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1960; 1 item (Box 17)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1960" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1961; 1 item (Box 17)
    White with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1961" in black.
  - Class of 1894 18th reunion pin, 1912; 1 item (Box 18)
    Orange and oval with "18th ANNUAL REUNION" in black; black ribbon with "'94" in gold.
  - Class of 1896 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    Yellow and round with "'96" and "Hello, Old Man, I'm glad to see you back" in black.
  - Class of 1902 25th reunion pin, 1927; 1 item (Box 18)
    Orange and round with "25TH REUNION '02" in black.
  - Class of 1946 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    Orange and round with "Princeton University, "'46" and "Bicentennial Class" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "Walt Snow" handwritten.
  - Alumni Council Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    White and rectangular with a drawing of a boat; "Alumni Council" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1930; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1930" in orange.
  - Class of 1930 30th reunion pin, 1960; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "30s 30th in 60" in black and orange; a caricature of a tiger on the background.
  - Reunion pin, 1931; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1931" in orange.
  - Class of 1931 25th reunion pin, 1956; 1 item (Box 27)
    Black and orange and round "1931" and "25th" in orange.
  - Class of 1931 35th reunion pin, 1966; 1 item (Box 27)
    Black and orange and round "1931" and "35th" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, 1932; 1 item (Box 27)
    Green and round with "Alumni Parade 1932" in white.
  - Class of 1932 40th reunion pin, 1972; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1932" and "40th" in black; with a tiger; "JIM DONNELL" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1932 45th reunion pin, 1977; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1932" and "45th Reunion" in black; with a tiger; "JIM DONNELL" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1933; 1 item (Box 27)
    Green and round with "Alumni Parade 1933" in black.
  - Class of 1933 15th reunion pin, 1948; 1 item (Box 27)
    "Fifteenth Reunion" and "1933" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "Bob Clifford" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1934; 1 item (Box 27)
    Light yellow and round with "Alumni Parade 1934" in navy.
  - Class of 1934 59th reunion pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "1934" in black; a drawing of a tiger in black and orange; a label "1993" attached; "MARY ATWATERKEER" handwritten.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 item (Box 27)
    Marine and round with "Alumni Parade 1935" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 item (Box 27)
    Brown and round with "Alumni Parade 1935" in white.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1937" in green.
  - Class of 1936 5th reunion pin, 1941; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Fifth Reunion," "'36" and seven 36's in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1937 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1937" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1938 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round, patterned on the baseball; with "Alumni," "1938" and "Parade" in black; orange and black ribbon.
  - Class of 1938 20th reunion pin, 1958; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1938" and "Twentieth Reunion" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1938 25th reunion pin, 1963; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1938," "25th Reunion" and "June 12-16 1963" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "AL HEINSOHN" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1938 35th reunion pin, 1973; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1938," "35th Reunion" and "June 7-10 1973" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "AL HEINSOHN" handwritten in green.
  - Reunion pin, 1939; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1939" in blue.
  - Class of 1939 22nd reunion pin, 1961; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and oval with "1939" and "Reunion June, 1961" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1939 Reunion pin, circa 1979; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1939 'XLISSIMO,'" "Original Combine," "A. P. G. A." and "'38 '40' '41 '42" in black; the "original combine" seal. Probably the 40th reunion pin of the class of 1939.
  - Class of 1939 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    Tiger and liquor bottle with "Vat 39".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1940; 1 item (Box 27)
    Light yellow and round with "Alumni Parade 1940" in brown.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1941; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with blue rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1941" in red.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1942; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with red rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1942" in blue.
  - Class of 1942 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and black with "Friar" and "'42" in black.
  - Class of 1943 40th reunion pin, 1983; 1 item (Box 27)
    Yellow and white and round; with "1943" and "40th Reunion June 2-4 1983" in black; "Augusta Radcliffe" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1944 39th reunion pin, 1983; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "1944" in black; a caricature of a tiger and a modified version of the Princeton seal and motto in black; a label "1983" attached.
  - Classes of 1939-1944 Reunion pin, 1983; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and yellow and round; with "'39, '40, '41, '42, '44," "Old Original Combine," and "Reunion June 2-4 1983" in black.
  - Class of 1945 50th reunion pin, 1995; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with the Princeton seal and motto; "John Kauffman" handwritten in black; a label "1995" attached.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1946; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with orange rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1946" in brown.
  - Class of 1946 20th reunion pin, 1966; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "20th Reunion" and "1946" in black; "Walt Snow" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1946 50th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "46's/50th" "The Legendary Bicentennial Class" in black; "REID BADGETT" hand written in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1947; 1 item (Box 27)
    Red and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1947" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1948; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1948" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1949; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1949" in black.
  - Class of 1949 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and orange and round with "1949 Playboy" in black; a drawing of a tiger smoking and drinking.
  - Class of 1949 Reunion pin, undated; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "The Automated Man" and "49" in orange; "Dan Lutzeier" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1951; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1951" in counter-shade.
  - Class of 1951 25th reunion pin, 1976; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with "The Revolutionary 25th" and "June 3-6, 1976" in black; "1951" in orange.
  - Class of 1951 45th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and rectangular "Princeton" and "1951" in orange; "45th Reunion" in black; a label "1996"; "Wiley Anderson" handwritten in black; a drawing of a tiger in an 18th-century costume.
  - Reunion pin, 1952; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1952" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1953; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1938" in counter-shade.
  - Reunion pin, 1954; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1954" in black; orange ribbon, "June 1954" and "Old Guard" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1955; 1 item (Box 27)
    Black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1955" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, 1956; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1956" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1957; 1 item (Box 27)
    Black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1957" in orange.
  - Class of 1957 20th reunion pin, 1977; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Paint the town with '57 in '77" in black; a drawing of a tiger painting.
  - Class of 1961 10th reunion pin, 1971; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "'61 in '71" in black.
  - Class of 1961 25th reunion pin, 1986; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with orange rim; "Princeton Class of 1961 25th Reunion" in black; a drawing of a tiger in orange and black; a label "Minor 1986"; "Ashley Magargee '62" handwritten.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1962; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1962" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1963; 1 item (Box 27)
    White with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1963" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1964; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1964" in black.
  - Class of 1965 5th reunion pin, 1970; 1 item (Box 27)
    Orange and round with "Princeton University," "'65" and "Fifth Reunion" in black; a label "1989" handwritten.
  - Class of 1966 25th reunion pin, 1991; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in a bow-tie; a label "Minor 1991"; Kathryn Barrows" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1966 30th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 27)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in a hat; "Overall 30th" and "On the Road to 250" in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1967; 1 item (Box 27)
    Black and round with "67" in tan.
  - Class of 1942 10th reunion pin, 1952; 1 item (Box 36)
    coral and black and round with "1942," "Jerry Horton" and "10th Reunion" counter-shaded.
  - Class of 1955 25th reunion pin, 1980; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "'55/25th" in black.
  - Class of 1955 30th reunion pin, 1985; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and black and round with "'55/30th" in white; a label "1985"; "Don Altmaier" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1955 40th reunion pin, 1995; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "'55/40th" in black; a label "Tom Graham, Jr".
  - Class of 1955 40th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "The Great Class 40th" and "Princeton 250th"in black; a label "1996"; a drawing of a tiger in black and orange.
  - Class of 1961 35th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "35th Reunion Celebrating 250 Great Years" in orange and black; a label "1996"; "Mary Conner" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1967 25th reunion pin, 1992; 1 item (Box 36)
    Gray and round with "Class of 1967," "Clear the Track" and "25th Reunion" in black; a label "1992"; "Dan White" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1971 25th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger on bicycle; "Saving the Wild Life. 1971's 25th Princeton's 250th" in orange and black; "Caley Schmierer" handwritten in black; a label "1996".
  - Class of 1971 25th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger on bicycle; a handwritten name illegible.
  - Class of 1972 5th reunion pin, 1977; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and rectangular with a tiger wearing a baseball cap; "'72's 5th" written in black.
  - Class of 1979 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "'79" in black.
  - Class of 1980 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "The Class of 1980" in white.
  - Class of 1980 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "PUP80" in white.
  - Class of 1981 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "P. U. 'Eighty One!" in brown and black.
  - Class of 1981 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with a tiger drawn in orange; "Princeton '81" in orange.
  - Class of 1982 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Yellow and round with "PU 82" in white and black.
  - Class of 1983 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with black rim; "83" in yellow and black.
  - Class of 1983 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with two beer mugs bearing "8" and "3" in black; "I Survived Another Party" in black.
  - Class of 1984 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "1984... Is here" in orange.
  - Class of 1985 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with a tiger and "1985" in black.
  - Class of 1986 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "We Made It! P '86" in black.
  - Class of 1986 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "86" in black and with 3 tigers looking out of the holes of the numerals.
  - Class of 1986 10th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "X" and "Marks the Spot" in black, over laid on "86" in orange".
  - Class of 1987 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1987" in orange.
  - Class of 1988 Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "Welcome to the Great Class of 1988 to the Alumni Council" in black.
  - Class of 1989 Reunion pin, circa 1989; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1989 Princeton University" in orange.
  - Class of 1990 5th reunion pin, 1995; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger on a director's chair with a bullhorn marked "5th"; "Lights!," "Camera!," "Action!" in orange and black; "Josh Empson" handwritten in black; a label "1995".
  - Class of 1990 Reunion pin, circa 1991-2000; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "The Class of 1990 Princeton University" in black.
  - Class of 1991 Reunion pin, circa 1991; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1991 Princeton University" in orange.
  - Class of 1927 60th reunion pin, 1987; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and rectangular with "Class of 1927" in orange; with a photograph of A. Whitaker (1927); "Al Whitaker" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1991 5th reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger; "Class of 1991 5th Reunion" in black.
  - Class of 1993 Reunion pin, circa 1993; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1993 Princeton University" in orange.
  - Class of 1993 Reunion pin, 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger seated on "93"; with "Gwen Prothro" in black; a label "1993".
  - Class of 1994 Reunion pin, circa 1994; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a drawing of the Princeton seal; "94" in orange.
  - Class of 1995 Reunion pin, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1995 Princeton University" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, 1994; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a drawing of Cleveland Tower and a tiger; "Graduate Alumni" in black and "94" watermarked in orange; a label "1994"; "Paul" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in Da Vinci's study mode; "Graduate Alumni," "1996 Reunion" in orange; "Deborah Schildkraut" handwritten in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, 1997; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with a drawing of a tiger in Da Vinci's study mode; "Graduate Alumni," "1997 Reunion" in orange; "Sue Kim" handwritten in black; a label "1997".
  - Graduate Alumni Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Conference" in black.
  - National Alumni Association Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and rectangular with "Princeton University National Alumni Ass'n" in black; "Jerry Horton '42" inlaid.
  - Battle Monument Dedication Ribbon, 1922-06-09; 1 item (Box 36)
    Red, white and blue, and round; "Usher Dedication of the Princeton Battle Monument June 9, 1922" in golden.
  - McCosh Pin, circa 1988; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with President J. McCosh's photograph inset; "1868--D. James McCosh, President, Educator, Philosopher--1888" in black.
  - Dickinson and Patton Pin, 1896; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with Presidents J. Dickinson's and F. L. Patton's photographs, with "Dickinson and Patton" in countercolor; "1746-1896" in black.
  - Championship Dinner Pin, 1926; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with a drawing of a tiger; "P. 36-H. 0 P. 25-Y.12 Championship Dinner New York City January 8th 1926" in black.
  - Communiversity Staff Pin, 1985; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a drawing of the FitzRandolph Gate and Nassau Hall; "Communiversity April 27, 1985 Staff" in black.
  - Princeton Parent Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with black rim; "I'm a Proud Princeton Parent" in black.
  - Beat Dartmouth Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and rectangular; "Beat Dartmouth" in black.
  - Beat Harvard Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round; "Beat Harvard" in black.
  - Beat Yale Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round; "Beat Yale" in black.
  - Bullish on Princeton Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and oval; "I'm Bullish on Princeton" in black.
  - Games Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round; "'B. T. C.!'" and "Compete! Games" in black.
  - Campaign for Princeton Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Round with Princeton seal in orange and black; "A Campaign for Princeton" in white.
  - Food is Energy Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with a tiger having an ice cream cone; "Food I$ Energy Don't Wa$te It!" in black.
  - Bring Back the Old Princeton Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "Bring Back the Old Princeton" in black.
  - Princeton Wrestling Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with "Save Princeton Wrestling" in orange.
  - Take Back the Night Pin, 1992; 1 item (Box 36)
    Navy and round with "take back the night" mark; "Princeton Unite! Take Back the Night April 25, 1992" in white.
  - Project 83 Pin, 1983; 1 item (Box 36)
    Black and round with a tiger; Orange "V" overlaid with "Project 83" in black.
  - Project 88 Pin, 1988; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "Project Eighty Eight." in black, orange and white.
  - Project 89 Pin, 1989; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with "Project 89" in orange and black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Bronze name tag with Princeton seal and motto on top; an insert typed "Timothy N. Pfeiffer" (Class of 1937).
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with orange and black rims; with a tiger.
  - Un-Curl Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with "Un-Curl" in black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and black; round with "Princeton" countershaded.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with black rim; "P" in black; "Brown -* *- Princeton" in black on orange ribbon.
  - St. Louis Alumni Pin, 1921; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with an orange bow on top; "National Alumni Ass'n Princeton University St. Louis February 11-12, 1921" in black; "Gordon Rentschler '07" handwritten with pencil.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 36)
    Orange and round with black ruffle around.
  - Staff Picnic Pin, 1993; 1 item (Box 36)
    White and round with a tiger wearing sunglasses; "Princeton University Staff Picnic June 10, 1993" in black; with a purple ribbon attached, "Judge" in silver.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 39)
    Orange and round with unrecognized figures in black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 item (Box 40)
    Black and round with an orange band across, "Princeton" in black; orange and black ribbon attached.
  - Class of 1889 Ribbon, 1895; 1 item (Box 40)
    Orange and rectangular; "'89 Sexennial June 10th, 1895" in black.
  - Ribbon, 1896; 1 item (Box 41)
    Orange and rectangular, with white pennant of Princeton seal and motto and "1746" and "1896," attached.